Hello hello friends welcome to our channel
Tomorrow Guys today I have brought
a new video for you guys so today I am going to talk
about ICICI Lombard Health Advantage Plan this plan was earlier
used by Indian soldiers but now
ICICI Lombard has taken over the Indian company in
September 2021 after that after
modifying some plans according to their own needs they
relaunched it in 2021
one of them is
Advantage I am going to do a full review about it
friends some features in this line are
very good like you can customize this
plan as per your needs
and can get it done as per your budget
before starting the video let me tell you I am
Vishal and I make videos after doing a lot of study abroad there is a
lot of detail for your knowledge and awareness and
I have made it in a very easy way to understand
subscribe if you visit my channel for the first time then
type all this
you will get the latest video first and also like
and share so let's start first of all  Let's do
this plan, let's
talk about it first of all, there will be an
entry in the middle
which will
be Meghnad, 6
subscribers
can also renew the appointed policy, if we talk about independence then if we
talk about subscription then friends
now the
appointed in the skin
is Remain Loyal, inside Apex Prime you
cannot subscribe to this meeting three more subscribe and subscribe Meghnad, if you take it then
you should subscribe to this channel
member no subscriptions
Vikram, so you can use the policy terms as per your budget and
your requirement, there is an option
of one year also, there is an option of
2 years also, maximum
option of 3 years also, we will talk about a multi-purpose
discount, if you
take a 198 policy for 2 years then you will have to take the second year
's policy, on that you will get a
discount of 7.5 percent and if you take a policy for 3 years then
you will get a discount of 10% on the third year's premium,
if we talk about the balance program then in
this policy you will get a
discount of 5 percent at the time of renewal, if you  If we
talk about annual awards function, then it
is available under this policy. If we
talk about room rent limit of Rs. 1000, then definitely subscribe to this
channel. If you
subscribe, then I will
explain what is its benefit. If you do
not take No Claim Bonus under
this, then you get No Claim Bonus. Whether
you take it or not, Indian companies subscribe to 20
celebrities for a
maximum of Rs. 10,000 and you will
get the ghee you have taken under the subscription. You should subscribe to this,
whichever is less of these two. In the subscription, the
company will pay you. Whatever you
say, you will have to get it done in a network hospital.
In the same condition, the company will
pay you. There
is also an option to get a newborn baby test done. For this, you will
not have to go to Noida hospital. If you
want, after getting maternity cover, you can get your baby
vaccinated for newborn
baby. If your child is below 101 years of age, then
for him the company will
do the vaccination on one or more companies. There is an
option to get a personal accident done
or a
permanent accident done.  Don't forget to subscribe to Total Disable or
Subscribe
and if
you have a date with such a DJ, then
in that condition the company will be your Jaisalmer Road and
it will present it to you so that
you don't face any kind of pressure on your loan like MI etc.,
you can easily pay it,
friends, as I told you, you
can customize this line as per your need,
so here customization
is also available to you, you
can reduce your waiting period as per your need, you can subscribe to the pre-existing
option given in this,
you can customize here also by paying a
little
premium in the company for this, you can get it done for one year, if we talk about
free and post hospitalization, then the
company has made husband and
wife free, if we talk about post hospitalization, then it has been made
600, so you can subscribe,
why talk about payment option, then all these
levels, if you feel that you are very
sick  If yes, then to reduce your premium,
you can give the payment option of 10
percent or 20 percent, that will
reduce your premium, but in that condition,
whatever payment you will use from your side in the hospital bill,
for example 20%, then
you will have to pay 20 percent out of one lakh and 80,000
companies will pay maternity
benefit, friends, you
can customize it as per your requirement, if you feel
that you need maternity benefit a little
early, then you can customize it as per your requirement, just
look at the last and
you will get the benefit in the Rolex variant, the company is
saying here that you will give this benefit for up to three deliveries,
if someone has twins,
then that delivery will be taken into account and
in this policy you will get up-to-date percentage, you
understand the complete 10 lakh rupees, the
best thing about this policy is that if
you take out the maternity benefit within 3 years  If you do not do this, then the
company will cut the maternity premium that
you have been offered, that is, they will
refund you and there is an option in this
that your meeting pimples, which is
run by 372 companies for years, by following a few steps
you can reduce your waiting list
to ninth. Now friends, let's talk about zone wise
pricing, then in Jeevan
like Delhi, Kolkata, Mumbai, Thane,
Pune and Hyderabad, apart from this Gujarat
State, Haryana and Rajasthan State
come under Jeevan. If we talk about Jaunpur, then all the
capitals in India for example
like Uttar Pradesh Capital Lucknow,
Patna of Bihar,
appoint in this way, if you have hatred in your mind then there is no
discount in Jeevan,
you can
subscribe
but by appointing here at the
minimum volume, if
you want to get your treatment done in June-12, then
if you go to Jeevan then
you will have to pay 15 per cent, if the
yoga of pregnancy
appointment is soon
then you should subscribe to this point,
I have given you the details about it,
friends, if you liked the video
then please like and subscribe
so that people  Reach here in this way and if
you do not forget to subscribe to my channel,
you will be the first to reach all the upcoming videos, then we will meet
in the next video, till then
bye-bye